const AnswersQuestions = [
  {
    question: "question1",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "question2",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "question3",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "question4",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "question5",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "question6",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "question7",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "question8",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "question9",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "question10",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "question11",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "question12",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "question13",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "question14",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "question15",
    answers: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
    trueAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
];

export default AnswersQuestions;
